That if you have to sell anything and
take an appointment for it, then we have to
face two tasks while calling, the first is
how to start the conversation and then
how do we start talking about our product in it, so
friends, today we are going to cover both the topics in two videos, those who are
talking, how to
start the conversation, be it an appointment or a
follow, so do watch this video till the end,
hello friends, always ahead always will,
friends, I welcome you again to the video of members in Hospitals and
Success Coach Insurance Celsius,
and
friends, if you are an insurance agent yet
and you have not joined our WhatsApp group, then do it, there are
very
good images and videos in it, which
you can send to your prospect, the link is
given in the description box, and now let me
talk about two types of calls we make to
our prospect, one is cold because
we do not know them, the other is
hot full, whom we know and
call them, in this video we are talking about warm calls,
whom we
know a little bit, we know a little bit, but
how do we start with them, so friends and calls
also  There are two types of calls, one is professional call and
one is friend call. Now,
they understand what professional calls or friend calls are.
Once in a workshop, I was asked that
Sir, whenever we talk to someone for insurance or for
taking an appointment,
they do not show interest, they do
not talk to us much, we only talk to them.
Then I replied to them that you
must be doing professional work, so professional
calls are those where there is only and only
talk of selling, only and only
talk of selling. Friends,
how are professional calls done in this,
if I give you an example of that, then the
first example is, I have
started working with this insurance company, when can I meet you, a
very good plan has come on pension,
when can I meet you, I want to meet you, I want to
talk about some financial planning, can
I come and meet you, I want to
talk about some insurance,
friends, in the same way we talk, where
we talk about perfect selling,
that is called a professional course
and let me tell you a research that
in today's time, every person attends at least three-four
such calls every day.  Where there is
talk of selling something to them, they get
irritated by it and it also gets recorded, so
friends, when that guy asked me the question
that people are not interested, then
I had replied that you
do a professional course and
when you talk in professional courses or in the beginning of selling, then the
customer never
takes interest, so what is the solution for this, you will have to
convert the professional course into a friends call, before what are friends calls,
its benefits were told that when
you make a friends call, the prospect will
easily start talking to himself,
your hesitation will reduce, what should I
talk about, what will happen, in this way your
interest will reduce and the
chances of getting an appointment will also increase, so friends,
whenever there is a professional call, that image chat
starts that friend, I have a script
and how to talk in this way,
but whenever there is a friends call,
you will have to do some preparations, you will have to do small
preparations, you will have to think
that how will I start, how will he
start talking to me, so for that, research is a must
And let me tell you, we all
cannot live without talking, but there are
some triggers which if pressed or provoked, then
any person
automatically starts talking. The first
trigger is interest if their interest is
discussed, the second way is benefit if
some of their benefits are discussed
and the third trigger is help if some help is
sought from them or some of their health is discussed,
whenever these three topics are left, every person will be ready
for you.
So friends, now you have to think about the
trigger point of the prospect you are talking to, what is their
interest area, that is, what should I talk about benefits
or what help should I ask from them or what
help should I provide. Friends, suppose if there is a
businessman, then where will their interest be?
In their business, they are not interested in your business, they are
not interested in what you do, it is their interest in their business.
If you talk about their business
and what are its prices,
what are its prices, I wanted to
find out, someone told me.  It is that you should
find out and tell me, in this way if you talk and
take interest in their business then they will
start talking to you, if they have made
some achievement and you start talking there then
they will be able to connect with you easily
and if there are any games that they
play and if you start talking there then
that is also a very good area of ​​interest,
they will easily talk to you,
its main benefit what benefit can you give them,
if they are businessmen then you have any
client with whom you can connect them, then
you can talk there or
how can you help them in their growth, is there any
webinar or seminar happening about which
you can give them information or help, you should
find out what help you can ask from them, it may
not be in the business area, it may be anything else, if you want to get
information about someone, to
know about a house, it can be anything, can
you help them or can
you take help from them,
definitely find out about it friends, helping is in the
nature of all of us, so when we ask for something, the
other person will automatically get interested,
whereas if I ask for the help of a teacher  If I talk about it, then
when you talk about their study area,
their subject, then they become
interested, be it some achievement or
they are playing a game all day or are
associated with some group somewhere and if
you talk about them there, then they become
interested quickly, about their benefits,
about their gang or
how they can progress, how many more children can they get
in their tuition, if you
talk about something like that then they become interested,
here you can ask us that so and so
child is his study level is weak or
what trick should we tell him so that his
state level improves, that is why I
called you, in this way when you
ask them for help or you help them, then
they become interested to talk to you,
similarly if there is a software
engineer, then you can talk to him about software, you can
talk about his achievements, they become interested,
about their benefits or
how to help them, how to fast, so
friends, you have to understand that encroachment is very
important, very  Another important
professional call is where we
discuss our interests, our benefits,
and we ask them for help, like,
give me a policy, or
buy my product. But friends, on the other hand,
where friends fall, we
discuss the other person's interests, talk about their
benefits, talk about
helping the other person,
and whenever we talk like this,
friends, the other person definitely
starts talking. Friends, I simply want to tell
you that you should do your homework. Write down the
names of up to 5 professionals that you have retained on your side and
ask yourself questions like, what is their interest,
what can I do to benefit them, and what can I do to help them?
Friends, if you find this out, then
definitely I am telling you that
your conversation will start very easily, and the other person will speak
more than you speak, and
your phase will be complete, where the conversation will
start well, now
how to make an appointment, in the meantime,
you have to change track.  If
you want to do this and set up a meeting there, then there are
two ways to approach it. First is an
easy approach and second is a professional approach, which
I will explain to you in the second part of this video,
which is coming next week. If it has come, then
you will find the link in the description box. So friends, if you have
n't subscribed to this channel yet, then definitely do it.
And if you have also activated the bell icon, then do it
because as soon as
those videos come, they will reach you first.
High Speed ​​MP RTO Online
Trading Dhanwan Waqt is helping every insurance
advisor, he is
achieving through it and
I share all his videos after every video of mine.
So this time also I will share a video of a student with
you.
Do watch it at the end of this video. Friends, this
training
is completely with money back guarantee. You can find out by calling these numbers with 6 days money back guarantee.
Friends,
if you liked the video, then definitely
press like. I will definitely wait for whatever you write in the comment box.
And friends, if you have
n't joined the WhatsApp group, then definitely do it with your friends.  If yes, then
put the link in the description box friends. Best wishes to all of you,
prayers, blessings, always style, always
stay ahead Sir, my name is Pawan Singh.
First of all, thanks to Amritsar and his entire team for giving
me the opportunity to learn and earn so much money from this course.
Even during the Corona period last year, I was
successful in selling 116 life insurance policies in Sikar through this. According to
me, this is a complete course,
every advisor should complete it once.
We thank God and his team. Please continue
such guidance in the future also.
Thank you Sir, now NAAC Travel Advisory has not become ordinary, that is,
high speed insurance
advisory because now it is getting ready
on advanced international models where insurance
advisors are doing research
on various subjects used in cells like
mind power, setting stop, IT systems,
tools and techniques, prospecting
strategy, meeting steps and technology
advancement, generation techniques, plan
presentation skills, objection having
skills with three plus objection following
skills through Singh Scans, reference KJS
and MDRCHOD.
Very effective in working on duties.  24
ways to increase your sales and income
start today here at Speed ​​& Jerry
Online Framing Dhanwan Bhavet and get money
back guarantee offer i.e. Lakshmi is
knocking at the door right now 1405 25252